questions = [
    { answer: "Angola", question: "Two equal horizontal bands of red and black, with a centered yellow emblem consisting of a five-pointed star within half a cogwheel crossed by a machete." },
    { answer: "Argentina", question: "Three horizontal bands of sky blue, white and sky blue. In the center is a radiant yellow sun with a human face known as the sun of may." },
    { answer: "Australia", question: "Blue with the union jack in the top left. There are 5 stars to the right of the union jack and 1 star underneath it." },
    { answer: "Austria", question: "Three equal horizontal bands of red, white and red." },
    { answer: "Bangladesh", question: "Green with a large red circle in the center." },
    { answer: "Barbados", question: "three equal vertical bands of blue, gold, and blue. With the head of a black trident centered on the gold band." },
    { answer: "Belgium", question: "three equal vertical bands of black, yellow, and red." },
    { answer: "Botswana", question: "light blue with a horizontal white-edged black stripe in the center." },
    { answer: "Brazil", question: "green with a large yellow diamond in the center bearing a blue celestial globe with 27 white five-pointed stars." },
    { answer: "Cameroon", question: "three equal vertical bands of green, red, and yellow, with a yellow five-pointed star centered in the red band." },
    { answer: "Canada", question: "two vertical bands of red with a white square between them. An 11-pointed red maple leaf is centered in the white square." },
    { answer: "China", question: "red with a large yellow five-pointed star and four smaller yellow five-pointed stars." },
    { answer: "Colombia", question: "three horizontal bands of yellow, blue, and red." },
    { answer: "Denmark", question: "red with a white cross that extends to the edges of the flag." },
    { answer: "Egypt", question: "three equal horizontal bands of red, white, and black. The gold Eagle of Saladin is centered in the white band." },
    { answer: "Estonia", question: "three equal horizontal bands of blue, black, and white." },
    { answer: "Finland", question: "white with a blue cross extending to the edges of the flag." },
    { answer: "France", question: "three equal vertical bands of blue, white, and red." },
    { answer: "Gabon", question: "three equal horizontal bands of green, yellow, and blue." },
    { answer: "Germany", question: "three equal horizontal bands of black, red, and gold." },
    { answer: "Greece", question: "Nine equal horizontal stripes of blue alternating with white. A blue square bearing a white cross appears in the upper left corner." },
    { answer: "Hungary", question: "three equal horizontal bands of red, white, and green." },
    { answer: "Iceland", question: "blue with a red cross outlined in white extending to the edges of the flag." },
    { answer: "India", question: "three equal horizontal bands of subdued orange, white, and green, with a blue chakra centered in the white band." },
    { answer: "Ireland", question: "three equal vertical bands of green, white, and orange." },
    { answer: "Isle of Man", question: "red with the Three Legs of Man emblem, in the center." },
    { answer: "Israel", question: "white with a blue six-pointed linear star centered between two equal horizontal blue bands near the top and bottom edges of the flag." },
    { answer: "Italy", question: "three equal vertical bands of green, white, and red" },
    { answer: "Jamaica", question: "diagonal yellow cross divides the flag into four triangles that are green and black." },
    { answer: "Japan", question: "white with a large red disk in the center" },
    { answer: "South Korea", question: "white with a red and blue yin-yang symbol in the center. There is a black trigram in each corner of the white field." },
    { answer: "Latvia", question: "three horizontal bands of maroon, white, and maroon." },
    { answer: "Malawi", question: "three equal horizontal bands of black, red, and green with a radiant, rising, red sun centered on the black band." },
    { answer: "Mexico", question: "three equal vertical bands of green, white, and red. There's a coat of arms is centered in the white band." },
    { answer: "Morocco", question: "red with a green pentacle known as Solomon's seal in the center of the flag." },
    { answer: "Netherlands", question: "three equal horizontal bands of red, white, and blue." },
    { answer: "New Zealand", question: "Blue with the union jack in the top left. There are 4 stars to the right of the union jack." },
    { answer: "Nigeria", question: "Three equal vertical bands of green, white, and green." },
    { answer: "Norway", question: "Red with a blue cross outlined in white that extends to the edges of the flag." },
    { answer: "Pakistan", question: "Green with a vertical white band on the left side. A large white crescent and star are centered in the green field." },
    { answer: "Poland", question: "Two equal horizontal bands of white and red." },
    { answer: "Portugal", question: "two vertical bands of green and red with the national coat of arms centered on the dividing line." },
    { answer: "Qatar", question: "Maroon with a broad white serrated band on the left side." },
    { answer: "Romania", question: "Three equal vertical bands of blue, yellow, and red." },
    { answer: "Russia", question: "Three equal horizontal bands of white, blue, and red." },
    { answer: "Senegal", question: "Three equal vertical bands of green, yellow, and red with a small green five-pointed star centered in the yellow band." },
    { answer: "Somalia", question: "Light blue with a large white five-pointed star in the center." },
    { answer: "South Africa", question: "Two equal width horizontal bands of red and blue separated by a central green band that splits into a horizontal Y. The Y embraces a black isosceles triangle." },
    { answer: "Spain", question: "Three horizontal bands of red, yellow, and red with the national coat of arms on the left side of the yellow band." },
    { answer: "Swaziland", question: "Three horizontal bands of blue, red, and blue. Centered in the red band is a large black and white shield." },
    { answer: "Sweden", question: "Blue with a golden yellow cross extending to the edges of the flag." },
    { answer: "Switzerland", question: "Red square with a bold, equilateral white cross in the center that does not extend to the edges of the flag." },
    { answer: "Tunisia", question: "Red with a white disk in the center bearing a red crescent nearly encircling a red five-pointed star." },
    { answer: "Turkey", question: "Red with a vertical white crescent moon and white five-pointed star centered just outside the crescent opening." },
    { answer: "Ukraine", question: "Two equal horizontal bands of light blue and yellow." },
    { answer: "United Kingdom", question: "Blue field with a red cross in the center. The cross has four red lines that run from the center of the cross to each corner of the flag. The red cross and lines are edged in white." },
    { answer: "United States", question: "13 equal horizontal stripes of red alternating with white. There is a blue rectangle in the upper left corner bearing 50 small, white, five-pointed stars." }
];

module.exports = {
    questions
};